iasplus.com 2010-06-11

# IAS Plus: Security, Legal, and Privacy

_Welcome_

Deloitte Touche Tohmatsu is delighted you're visiting our IAS Plus Website. By using this Website, you agree that you will abide by the below terms and conditions: 

_Legal_

**About Deloitte**

Deloitte Entities refers to one or more of Deloitte Touche Tohmatsu, a Swiss Verein, and its network of member firms, each of which is a legally separate and independent entity. Please see [www.deloitte.com/about](http://www.deloitte.com/about) for a detailed description of the legal structure of Deloitte Touche Tohmatsu and its member firms. 

"Deloitte" is the brand under which tens of thousands of dedicated professionals in independent firms throughout the world collaborate to provide audit, consulting, financial advisory, risk management, and tax services to selected clients. These firms are members of Deloitte Touche Tohmatsu (DTT), a Swiss Verein. Each member firm provides services in a particular geographic area and is subject to the laws and professional regulations of the particular country or countries in which it operates. DTT helps coordinate the activities of the member firms but does not itself provide services to clients. DTT and the member firms are separate and distinct legal entities, which cannot obligate the other entities. DTT and each DTT member firm are only liable for their own acts or omissions, and not those of each other. Each of the member firms operates under the names "Deloitte", "Deloitte & Touche", "Deloitte Touche Tohmatsu", or other related names. Each DTT member firm is structured differently in accordance with national laws, regulations, customary practice, and other factors, and may secure the provision of professional services in their territories through subsidiaries, affiliates and/or other entities. 

**Copyright**

© 2010 Deloitte Touche Tohmatsu. 

If you copy, print, or distribute pages or portions of pages from this Website, such pages and portions of pages are subject to the following conditions: 

  * They may used for informational purposes only. 
  * They may be used only for non-commercial purposes. 
  * They must include the above Copyright and below Disclaimer of Responsibility notices in their entirety. 

Note that any program, publication, design, product, process, software, technology, information, know-how, or idea described on this Website may be the subject of other rights, including other intellectual property rights, which are owned by Deloitte Entities or other interested parties and are not licensed to you hereunder. 

**Disclaimer of Responsibility**

This website and the information herein (the "Website") are provided by DTT and contains general information only on a subject or subjects. This Website is not an exhaustive or comprehensive treatment of any such subject(s) and is provided for informational purposes only with the understanding that you will read and adhere to the conditions of access contained herein. No Deloitte Entity is, by means of this Website, rendering accounting, business, financial, investment, legal, tax, or other professional advice or services. This Website is not a substitute for such professional advice or services, nor should it be used as a basis for any decision or action that may affect, among other things, your finances, your business or your compliance obligations. Before making any decision or taking any action that may affect your finances, your business or your compliance obligations, you should consult a qualified professional adviser. 

This Website is provided as is, and the Deloitte Entities make no express or implied representations or warranties regarding this Website. Without limiting the foregoing, the Deloitte Entities do not warrant that this Website will be accurate, complete or error-free or will meet any particular criteria of performance or quality. The Deloitte Entities accept no responsibility for updating the contents or any other aspect of this Website. Without limiting the foregoing, changes in regulations or requirements, whether statutory or otherwise, may have occurred subsequent to the time content in the Website was entered. The Deloitte Entities expressly disclaim any and all warranties, either express or implied, including, without limitation, warranties of merchantability, title, fitness for a particular purpose, non-infringement, compatibility, security, and accuracy. 

You may not rely upon this Website and any use of this Website is at the user's sole risk. The user assumes full responsibility and risk of loss resulting from the use of this Website. None of the Deloitte Entities, nor any of their respective personnel shall be responsible for any loss whatsoever sustained by any person or entity who uses or takes any action based upon this Website. By using this Website you agree to indemnify and hold harmless the Deloitte Entities. 

If any of the foregoing is not fully enforceable for any reason, such unenforceability shall not in any manner affect or render unenforceable the remainder and such unenforceable provision shall be deemed modified to the extent necessary to render it enforceable, preserving to the fullest extent permissible the intent set forth herein. 

The Deloitte Entities cannot and do not assure you in any way that this site is compatible with your computer equipment or that this site is free of errors, viruses, or similar defects. Nor do the Deloitte Entities warrant that this site will be available when you might want to get information from it, for reasons including system failure, updating, maintenance, or repair. 

**No Unlawful or Prohibited Use**

As a condition of your use of this Website, you agree that you will not use this Website or its content for any purpose that is unlawful or prohibited by these terms and conditions. 

**Trademarks**

"Deloitte Touche Tohmatsu", "Deloitte & Touche", "Deloitte", "Touche", "Tohmatsu", the Deloitte, Deloitte Touche Tohmatsu, and Deloitte & Touche logos (and any of the foregoing used in any combination), product names and all page headers, footers, and icons are trademarks or registered trademarks of Deloitte Entities. All other product names mentioned are the trademarks of their respective owners. 

The name "IAS Plus" and the  logo are trademarks of Deloitte Touche Tohmatsu. 

**Links from This Website to Other Sites**

No Deloitte Entity is responsible for the contents or use of any other websites that are referenced by this Website including, without limitation, the accuracy or reliability of any information, data, opinions, advice, or statements made on those websites. Links from this Website to other sites do not constitute an endorsement by any Deloitte Entities. Those links are for convenience only. It is the responsibility of the user to evaluate the content and usefulness of information obtained from other sites. 

**Linking to This Website from Another Site**

DTT permits anyone to link to our http://www.iasplus.com Website subject to the linker's compliance with the following terms and conditions. 

A site that links to the IAS Plus Website: 

  * May link to, but not replicate, content contained in the IAS Plus site; 
  * Must not present misleading or false information about the IAS Plus site or about any Deloitte Entity; 
  * Must not misrepresent any Deloitte Entity's relationship with the linker; 
  * Must not imply that any Deloitte Entity is endorsing or sponsoring the linker or the linker's services or products; 
  * Must not use any Deloitte Entity name or logo without prior written permission from the owner in each instance; 
  * May link only to web pages (extension of .htm) but not directly to documents (such as PDF or ZIP files); 
  * Must not contain content that could be construed as obscene, libelous, defamatory, pornographic, or inappropriate for all ages; 
  * Must not contain materials that would violate any laws; 
  * Must agree that the link may be removed at any time upon Deloitte DTT's request pursuant to DTT's reserved rights to rescind its consent to allow the link. 

_Privacy Statement_

DTT is a privacy conscious organization. The following privacy statement explains how DTT protects visitors' information gathered via this Website. If you as a visitor choose to register or submit information to this Website, you agree to use such data in accordance with this privacy statement. Please note that this site contains links to other sites, including, without limitation, sites maintained by other Deloitte Entities, which may not be governed by this privacy statement. 

If you have any questions regarding this privacy statement or do not feel that your concerns have been addressed, please direct your questions to **info@iasplus.com**. 

**Information Collection**

As a visitor, you do not have to submit any personal information in order to use the Website. The site collects only personally identifiable information that is specifically and voluntarily provided by visitors. Such information may consist of, but is not limited to, your name, current job title, company address, email address and telephone and fax numbers. 

DTT does not usually seek sensitive information (e.g., data relating to race or ethnic origin, religious beliefs, criminal record, physical or mental health, or sexual orientation) from visitors. DTT will, where necessary, obtain visitors' explicit consent to collect and use such information. 

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

To ensure that this Website is well managed and to facilitate improved navigation within the site, DTT or its service provider(s) may use cookies (small text files stored in a user's browser) or Web beacons (electronic images that allow the Website to count visitors who have accessed a particular page and to access certain cookies) to collect aggregate data. DTT may use such devices to track information on our systems and identify categories of visitors by items such as IP address, domain, browser type and pages visited. This information is reported to our webmasters who use the information to analyze the number of visitors to different areas of the site and to help make sure that this Website is serving as a useful, effective information source. 

Neither our cookies nor Web beacons collect any personal information such as your name or email address. Further, most browsers permit individuals to decline cookies. [Learn more about cookies and how to reject them](http://www.deloitte.com/dtt/article/0,1002,cid%253D29355,00.html). However, under specific circumstances, visitors may be denied access to some parts of our site if their browsers are set to decline cookies. 

**Information Use**

Personal information is used only for limited purposes. For example, when you register with the Website to gain access to premium content or request future communications about various Deloitte Entities' areas of interest, such as specific Deloitte Entity publications or marketing campaigns, DTT may use the information you submit to create a personal profile to customize the response to further requests or inquiries. DTT may also use the information to personalize your Website experience. In addition, when you choose to register online for a Deloitte Entity-hosted event, Deloitte Entities will use the information you submit to respond to you. In addition, the webmasters may, where necessary, use your information for various site related tasks. DTT will implement procedures to obtain necessary consents before sending you emails containing information about Deloitte Entity service offerings. You may at any time request that DTT discontinue sending you such materials. 

**Disclosure of Information to Third Parties**

Although DTT may provide visitors' information to service providers that handle information on DTT's behalf, DTT will usually not share the information with third parties or other Deloitte Entities for secondary or unrelated purposes unless otherwise disclosed at the point of collection. 

Personal information may be transmitted internationally through the Deloitte Entities or to third parties for the purposes identified above. This may include transfer to countries without data protection rules similar to those in effect in a visitor's country of residence. By providing information to DTT through this Website, you are consenting to such transfers. Where appropriate, personal information may be disclosed to law enforcement, regulatory or other government agencies, or third parties where necessary or desirable to comply with legal or regulatory obligations or requests or for the purposes identified above. 

**Access to Information**

This Website collects data from you in only two circumstances – if you choose to access IFRS E-learning or if you choose to subscribe to the IAS Plus Newsletter and Alerts. Visitors who do either of those things may change their details as follows: 

  * _IFRS E-learning._ The IFRS E-learning page (accessed by clicking on the light bulb icon on the home page – or [Click Here](http://www.deloitteifrslearning.com/)) has a 'Delete my registration details' button. 
  * _Subscribing to the newsletters and alerts._ The IAS Plus subscription page for newsletters and alerts is accessed by clicking on the link 'Click to subscribe to IAS Plus newsletter and alerts by email' on the home page (or Click Here). The email you receive transmitting each newsletter or alert includes an 'Unsubscribe' link. 

**Information Security**

DTT has in place reasonable commercial standards of technology and operational security to protect all information provided by visitors from loss, misuse, alteration or destruction. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

DTT reserves the right to modify or amend this privacy statement at any time and for any reason. Nothing contained herein creates or is intended to create a contract or agreement between any Deloitte Entity and any user visiting the Website or providing identifying information of any kind. 

**Children's Privacy Protection**

DTT understands the importance of protecting children's privacy in the interactive online world. This Website is not designed for or intentionally targeted at children 13 years of age or younger. It is not DTT's policy to intentionally collect or maintain information about anyone under the age of 13. 

**Visitors' Questions**

If you have any questions or concerns regarding your privacy while using this Website, please direct them to the [IAS Plus Webmaster](mailto:info@iasplus.com) (info at iasplus.com).
